Contact

+919972413758 (Home) dandagi.arjun95@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/arjundandagi (LinkedIn) arjundandagi.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Python (Programming Language)
Terraform

Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi

Kannada

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

Bash Scripting and Shell programing
The Neuroscience of Learning

AWS Certified Developer - Associate

Completion Award for Oracle MOOC: Managing Java Cloud Services Using REST

Arjun Dandagi

DevOps AWS △#(CDA,CSA) | Python | Terraform | Packer | Docker | Jenkins | Ansible | ELK | Rancher | Kubernetes | Bash Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Experienced DevOps Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunications industry. Skilled in Python, Terraform, Docker, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Java. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused on Computer Science from PES University.

Experience

Uninstall.io
DevOps Developer
January 2019 - Present
Bangaon Area, India

working as a DevOps Engineer for the largest Singapore Healthcare startup (MaNaDr https://manadr.com),

Technology stack involves

1. AWS for the infrastructure

Got certified as *AWS Solutions architect associate* in May 2019

- 2. Terraform to automate the AWS infra provisioning
- 3. i) Ansible
- ii) Packer for the AMI preparation of the application service
- 4. Jenkins for the CICD, both infra and application deployments.
- 5. Docker and Kubernetes being evaluated in the pre-prod setup in GKE
- 6. GCP, running staging workloads in a Google Compute platform
- 7. Monitoring via Grafana, Collectd
- 8. Log Collection via ELK (elastic and kibana managed service in AWS, filebeat, and log stash for processing)
- 9. we use AWS SSM for server logins, and evaluating on complete removal of SSH keys and only relying on AWS Systems Manager.

My learning never stops even outside the work, though I haven't applied the below technologies in the work I have gained the skill by performing my HandsOn learning

1. EKS

2. helm charts to automate the Kubernetes config files

Telstra

IT Developer

July 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Was part of the Development team at the beginning. working on JAVA technology using SpringBoot to write microservice, learned AWS technology and got certified as AWS Developer Associate.

got interested in docker and technology toolset and thereafter moved to work

- 1. Docker
- 2. Rancher
- 3. Bamboo
- 4. Bash
- 5. AWS
- 6. Terraform

automated blue-green deployment in rancher via bamboo.

gained a good amount of DevOps toolset. and thought of progressing in career as DevOps :)

GetGo

QA at GetGo (formerly part of citrix) February 2017 - June 2017 (5 months)

Bangalore

worked on a testing framework like Selenium using Java technology. was part of the GOTO webinar team. work on testing attendee reports, schedule timings etc

Education

PES University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2013 - 2017)

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya haveri

· (2006 - 2012)